I want to breath. I hate this night.
I want to wake up. I hate being in dream.
Locked in me, I am dead.
Don’t wanna be lonely. Just wanna be yours
Why is it so dark here without you?
It's dangerous, broken my figure.
Save me, I can't hold myself. Can't.
Listen to my heart beat. It's calling you at it's own will.
In this black darkness you are shining so bright.
Give me your hands, save me, save me. I need your love before I fall, fall
Give me your hands, save me, save me.
Tonight, moon shines more than usual. Vacant room in my memory.
This lunatic night swallows me. Please save me tonight.
Please save me to night. Please save me to night
In this childish craziness you can only save me tonight.
I have known that you are my savior, the part of me and only hands cover my sorrow
The best of me. I have only you
Please level up your voice to make me laugh again. play on
Listen to my heart beat. It's calling you at it's own will.
In this black darkness you are shining so bright.
Give me your hands, save me, save me. I need your love before I fall, fall
Give me your hands, save me, save me.
Thank you for making me myself. Making me be able to fly.
Giving me wings. Ironing me who was wrinkled.
Breaking me who was stuffy. Waking me up who was in dream.
Whenever I think about you sun is shining. And I throw away my sorrow.
Thank you. Be ourselves.
Give me your hands, save me, save me. I need your love before I fall, fall